<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-15"?>
<rss xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Renés Blog</title>
    <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/o2/rss/blog?blog_id=5;tree_id=42218</link>
    <ttl>15</ttl>
    <image>
      <title>o2 Portal</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica</link>
      <url>http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg</url>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Keep focused on our change</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/56006/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Our Change Champions in Hamburg and Rostock Hi colleagues, You are aware that we are facing challenging times in which we need to do things differently, much faster and in a more focused manner than we have done before. Now is the time for all of us who have creative ideas and the courage to make a difference and change our company and the way we work. Our more than 240 Change Champions are a very good example for this new kind of thinking and acting. Here is a video recorded and produced by our colleagues in Hamburg and Rostock. I am very impressed by this initiative and fully support it! Have a look! Watch our Change Champions in action!  Be More With Telefónica's 'Be More' program and the 3 Ds - Discover, Disrupt, Deliver - we have the right approach and the right attitudes in place to further drive the transformation of our company. And our 'Einfach machen' claim perfectly fits into it. You will see lots of information on 'Be more' and ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-08-05 18:00:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>360</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's your Big Idea?</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/55989/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Hi everyone, Our company holds a vast number of creative minds! Following our Big Idea competition, you've once again proved this fact by handing in numerous constructive ideas. I'm impressed with what we've received so far and I'm pretty sure that there's more to come. Many of you might still be working on your submission, but I would like to remind you that you now only have two more weeks before the competition deadline. Our mailbox will be open for your ideas until 12th August 7pm . Thank you for your effort so far and best of luck to all of you. Keep those ideas coming! Eva and the whole European Management Team are really looking forward to seeing the winning entry. Let's make it a Telefónica Deutschland one! Rene Deutsche &amp;#220;bersetzung Was ist Deine &amp;quot;Big Idea&amp;quot;? Hallo Zusammen, es gibt in unserem Unternehmen eine enorme Anzahl kreativer K&amp;#246;pfe! Ihr zeigt dies erneut eindrucksvoll im &amp;quot;Big Idea&amp;quot; Wettbewerb ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-08-01 12:15:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>358</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Danke!</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/55925/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Dear colleagues, What a day for our company! And what an incredible accomplishment for the team who made this historical moment happen. After enormous efforts and outrageous team play we were able to make a strong offer and sign a deal with KPN within just a few days and nights. A lot of people who have gone the extra mile these last days! Be it Legal, Strategy, Finance, Regulatory, Comms, Marketing, Service &amp;amp; Sales, ST, NT or HR ... the effort and commitment was simply astonishing. I would like to thank you for your truly fantastic hard work, outstanding commitment and professionalism as a team! This is the first step on this journey. By carrying on this spirit and focus, we will make this a fantastic success! Rene Liebe Kolleginnen und Kollegen, Was f&amp;#252;r ein gro&amp;#223;artiger Tag f&amp;#252;r unser Unternehmen! Und was f&amp;#252;r eine herausragende Leistung des Teams, das diesen historischen Moment m&amp;#246;glich gemacht hat! Dank harter Arbeit und unglaublichem Teamwork konnten wir ein starkes Angebot vorlegen und ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-07-23 11:15:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>355</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The digital revolution </title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/55617/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>During the CEO breakfast Dear colleagues, During my last visit in Berlin a week ago, together with Joachim, Valentina and Tim from our Berlin office, I met high level political and business representatives at the 'CEO_Breakfast'. We presented some facts from our recent Millennial survey and talked about how the digital generation will change our society and our economy. To become a digital Telco we need to understand our customers, business-partners, and not least future employees because they will not adapt to the world as they grow older - but the world and we have to adapt to them! New spirit According to the results of our Millennial survey the digital generation likes to work in start-ups instead of established companies and for those businesses who do marketing via social media instead of large sales departments. And this generation is keener on receiving the latest generation of smartphone instead of a fancy company car. But millennials are also concerned about current events in ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-07-05 17:00:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>353</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become a Black Belt!</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/55517/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Become a Black Belt! Hi colleagues, I am sure, you have seen the story on our last Lean Six Sigma Certification &amp;amp; Community Event that took place end of April. At that event 10 new colleagues received their Black Belt certificates. Congratulations once again! Together, all 45 Black Belts are now in all units of our organization optimizing our processes and doing project and change management as well as analytics. That is great and the Operational Excellence Programme is so effective and successful, that the Management Board decided to extend it and to qualify 100 Black Belts and 280 Green Belts by 2015! We are doing this because it is absolutely crucial for us to have standardized processes and a fundamental operating methodology on how we run our company and above all key for our growth. Apply now! Becoming a Black or Green Belt is your chance to change not only one or more processes but our way we operate day by day! It is your opportunity to change our company! ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-06-27 11:15:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>351</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Be different, be diverse!</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/55458/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Great discussions at the Diversity Day Dear colleagues, Last Tuesday was the first German Diversity Day and together with Joachim and 20 colleagues we talked about diverse employee structures and what makes a good work life balance. I was very impressed by the open discussion and your input. Thank you very much! Mixed ecosystem of people Diversity is about multiple topics beyond gender and age towards the people and a cultural change. It is therefore our management's job to create a mixed ecosystem of people: For example, we want to increase the number of employees with disabilities. At the moment out of approximately 5.300 employees in Germany we only hire about 100 people with serious disabilities - that is a quote of 1.7 percent. Another example is nationality. Diverse teams perform better: To this reason, colleagues from other OBs like the Czech Republic will join our teams in Germany. Fresh eyes and new ideas Another point is age: we need more young people! To be agile, we need our ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-06-19 15:30:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>349</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Concept Store - think big</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/55381/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>With Markus Sardison, Julius Korn, Salahdin, Hans und Baran Dear colleagues, Our new concept store in Berlin is mainly one thing: A world of digital experiences. Here, our customers experience hands-on the possible digital uses of our products - and our enthusiastic O&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; Gurus are doing a great job in facilitating this experience to customers! In this digital world our Think Big young people are at home. Julius Korn (24), for example, first introduced the idea of a football network wo-wird-gekickt.de at Think Big. Now that his website is online, Julius is now considering creating an app. Also the three guys from Berlin Salahdin Said, Hans Storck and Baran Keskin (all 20) put the website &amp;quot;World Citizen&amp;quot; online with support of our youth program. With this project they want to reduce prejudice towards citizens with immigrant background by promoting and running workshops, discussions and dialogs. Because we are all - and I strongly agree with ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-06-11 18:25:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>346</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the millennials matter</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/55284/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Dear colleagues, today I attended this year's ZEIT Conference in Berlin. I discussed with young entrepreneurs and experts in personal management how the digital generation changes our world. Who is this digital generation? Millennials grew up at the start of our digital world. This digital revolution - the breakthrough of the mobile Internet, of smartphones, tablets and Social Media - has been the biggest technology watershed since the invention of the computer. And it is profoundly shaping businesses and our markets in particular: Millenials today account for 88 million of our customers worldwide. And they are technology trendsetters. Getting in touch with friends all over the world anytime and anywhere, having access to an infinite pool of information and digital services - what's natural for millennials becomes more and more habitual for other generations as well. Millennials also change our business world as employees. They introduce a new entrepreneurial spirit in the business world: ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-06-06 17:00:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>344</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technik Tag in Teltow</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/55171/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Richtfunksammler am Teltower Standort It has been some months ago that I have been in Teltow last time. So, Wednesday schedule was booked for the NT and Sales colleagues at our site in Nord-Ost. Of course LTE and data were the topics to talk about: The network colleagues updated me on LTE rollout and technology ;-) They are mastering a challenge for the whole company. Because this technology enables us to handle the data usage of the future - in the US the data usage per LTE smartphone and month reaches 1,4 GB!! We have to monetize this data appetite - with smart marketing ideas providing the right data snacks for our customers with the right prize tag. Thank you to all NT colleagues in Teltow and all other sites for planning, building and running our future! And thank you for a sunny Technik-Tag in Teltow, I really enjoyed it! Rene Mit Frank Berlin - Manager Mobile Access Integration Mit Oliver Tananow - Lead Elektrotechnik - Blitzschutz Dennis Frischen - Operator Mobile Access R&amp;#252;diger ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-05-31 12:40:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>342</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Champions-League-Final</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/55116/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <pubDate>2013-05-23 15:30:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>340</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanks for a great AGM!</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/54899/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>During the AGM Hi colleagues, Here are some impressions from our first Annual General Meeting (AGM) that took place on 7th May. The AGM is not only a key event for our company but also for our shareholders as this is their opportunity to get first-hand information on Telefónica Deutschland and to exercise their rights. Together with Rachel and Markus, I answered the questions of our shareholders and shared with them our view on the current market situation, our 2012 and recent business performance and explained how we intend to further transform our company to achieve our business and financial goals. Especially the changes in our customers' behaviour have a deep impact on our strategy as data services are becoming more important than ever and the usage of SMS declines significantly. At the same time, the commercial environment in the German market is becoming even more active and competitive. Our competitors are heavily investing in the sales channels in order to gain market share. Moreover, ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-05-17 10:45:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>338</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Tanguy!</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/54822/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Dear colleagues I would like to share with you all an update regarding a change in my direct team. Nina Kreuzpointner is moving on from her current role as my Executive Assistant/Referent. Starting 2.5., she will be responsible for Multichannel Strategy &amp;amp; Projects within the Sales &amp;amp; Service team. I would like thank her for her dedication and excellent work for me and the whole Management team over the last three years. Rock on! I am delighted to announce that Tanguy Rohou will take over from Nina as my Executive Assistant with immediate effect. Tanguy brings with him great insights and knowledge of our global company having held previous positions in Telefónica Digital based in Spain and Telefónica UK. He is joining from the German Financial Services team where he has been working for the past year. I would like to congratulate both of them on their new roles and wish them all the best. Welcome Tanguy, thank you Nina - see you around ! René Willkommen Tanguy! Liebe Kollegen, ich m&amp;#246;chte ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-05-07 11:00:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>336</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Messaging-services outdistance SMS</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/54800/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Hi colleagues, OTT companies have launched new products and services that are attacking our classical products and services - just think of Whatsapp, iMessage, or the new Facebook Messenger. A study published a few days ago underlines radical change in customer behavior: According Informa, daily OTT messaging traffic has already overtaken daily SMS traffic. An average of 19 billion OTT messages are sent per day in 2012, compared with an average of around 17 billion SMS messages. And this trend is set to continue, the study highlights: The volume of OTT messaging traffic is set to be twice that of SMS by the end of the year. By the end of 2013, the study estimates that 41 billion OTT messages will be sent every day, compared with an average of about 19 billion SMS messages. This shows how rapidly the market is changing. It has taken OTT messaging just about five years to reach this point - BlackBerry Messenger was launched in 2007, while the first SMS was sent 20 years ago. Even though the ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-05-03 09:45:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>334</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't be too late, better be early!</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/54734/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Hi colleagues, Last week all 9 projects currently working in our Wayra Academy here in Munich presented their ideas and first business results in 3-minute-pitches to the Management Board and interested employees. It was really good to see the enthusiasm, the spirit and the passion of these young founders! They are role models and embrace digitization and entrepreneurship. But as the market environment is really tough and only a few become successful, they have to position their startup. And they have to convince investors why they are different than other companies. Here it is also absolutely ok to say: &amp;quot;I am like Paypal, but with a twist, and this is how we differentiate...&amp;quot; Differentiation and understanding of customer needs is the name of the game. And here the motto is: don't be too late, better be early! With Wayra we are supporting ideas and young innovative companies that will change the future. Together with Telefónica and Telefónica Digital we are using this creative potential ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-04-23 11:15:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>327</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That's transformation</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/54423/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <pubDate>2013-03-15 11:30:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>325</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saludos from the Mobile World Congress</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/54230/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Every year, it's really exciting to see the enthusiasm for smartphones and fast networks growing. And every year we as Telefónica are at the forefront supporting our customers to make their lives easier. During the press conference at MWC Yesterday, together with Oliver Schmitt, I presented our roll-out plans for LTE in Germany and our efforts to further optimize our mobile broadband infrastructure. We also talked about our brand new &amp;quot;Live Check&amp;quot;-Service: it brings more transparency for our customers and shows how well our o2 mobile network is working in their area. Furthermore we asked &amp;quot;How digital do you want to be?&amp;quot; and explained our revolutionary new tariff model. With it we meet the demands of our customers by freeing them from all thoughts about their mobile voice and text usage. They just have to choose the size of their data packet to access to the digital world of unlimited possibilities. Find out the details on our recent activities on the Intranet ! Please also have a look at ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-02-26 17:15:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>321</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kick off 2013</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/53971/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Dear colleagues, I hope you had a great start into 2013. In the last days and weeks a lot of Kick off events took place in the units and for our Top 500 management team. You will read about them on our intranet very soon. The target and the priorities for this year are very clear and the leadership team is asked to communicate them through the organization: Most important: We want to be the fastest growing mobile service provider and deliver superior cash flow! We will achieve that by pushing LTE &amp;amp; monetize data in all segments capitalizing our multi-brand portfolio and delivering superior customer satisfaction and transforming into an efficient, execution driven responsible organization. During our group work at the Top 500 event With regard to our transformation activities we achieved our market share growth and our efficiency targets by having changed ourselves. That is great! But we have to continue our efforts because there is no way back in our industry to the &amp;quot;good old times&amp;quot;. We ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-02-06 16:30:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>317</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your smartphone is a supermarket</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/53862/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Dear colleagues! On stage Greetings from this year's DLD conference under the motto &amp;quot;Patterns that Connect&amp;quot;. Today, in an interview and during a discussion I made clear that mobile shopping and payment with your smartphone is the next big thing in the mobile revolution. We will more and more use our smartphone as a safe and convenient way to make daily payments. And we are not talking about a distant future: This technology is now happening in Germany. In conversation with Dr. Hubert Burda Since October last year mpass-customers can pay contactless via mobile phone in thousands of stores in Germany and abroad. With mpass , we are the first network provider to offer mobile payment in Germany in retail and it is part of our financial service ecosystem we are building around the four pillars: Direct-to-Bill, Financial products &amp;amp; services, mpass and Infrastructure partnerships. And mpass is just the first step: With O&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; Wallet , which will start mid-February with a friendly user test, we ...</description>
      <pubDate>2013-01-21 16:30:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>314</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Change the rules"</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/53729/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Dear colleagues, have you ever thought about changing the rules? Taking the courage to do things differently, to gain new perspectives and insights? This morning I met up with our Top Talents who have now successfully completed the current round of this programme. I really enjoyed the conversations we had. These 12 colleagues had the courage and the determination to do things differently when they started the Top Talent programme 18 months ago. They left their &amp;quot;home&amp;quot; department, went on national and international rotations and got to know new business units, new processes, and new colleagues. All of them took the programme as a chance to develop their career to the next level. This deserves a big &amp;quot;Chapeau&amp;quot;! Stefanie M&amp;#252;ller-H&amp;#246;lzle (ganz links), René (Mitte) und Susanne Kolbe (ganz rechts) &amp;#252;bergaben den Top Talents ihre Abschlusszertifikate: Gerhard Kleiner, Bernd Vollmayr, Carla Helferich, Anu Aurich, Oliver Kl&amp;#246;ckner (v.l.n.r.)* All of them underlined the importance of exchange, networking, ...</description>
      <pubDate>2012-12-19 11:15:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>312</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy birthday SMS</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/53624/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <pubDate>2012-12-03 16:40:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>310</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Management</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/53587/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <pubDate>2012-11-26 13:45:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>308</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SZ Führungstreffen</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/53578/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Dear colleagues, Last week I met many fellow CEOs at the &amp;quot;SZ F&amp;#252;hrungstreffen Wirtschaft&amp;quot; in Berlin. I was invited to speak on the panel on Social Media with J&amp;#252;rgen Wilhelm, the Chairman of Bayerischer Rundfunk (BR), Christoph Bornschein, CEO of Social Media consultancy TLGG, and Kurt Kister, the Editor in Chief of S&amp;#252;ddeutsche Zeitung. We had a lively discussion on how Social Media changes the way we as companies interact with our customers - ranging from the shift in power it brings to topics like data protection and entrepreneurship in Germany. We here at Telefónica have made great progress with our Social Media strategy and learned a lot from the customer feedback in our forum, idea portal, and our presence on key sites as Facebook and Twitter. My main points were: Every CEO of a company has to take Social Media seriously, use it himself and listen to the customers. Why? Because companies need to take part in Social Media. They have to be present in the Social Media channels where their ...</description>
      <pubDate>2012-11-21 15:45:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>305</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our first quarterly results as a listed company</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/53489/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <description>Dear colleagues, After the exciting day at the Frankfurt Stock Exchange last week, we can celebrate our next premiere today: Our first presentation of quarterly results as a listed company! The results are strong and underline our successful growth story. And by the way: They match the development of our stock price since the first day - which looks pretty good. Compared to Q3 / 2011, we added 10.3% more contract customers. The prepaid business also continued to grow, doubling its new customers compared with the previous quarter. Overall, we generated a healthy OIBDA growth of 12.5% compared to the third quarter of last year. Wireless service revenue increased 5.6 percent compared with the third quarter of 2011 to reach 812 million euro - here we are number three in the market! Successful mobile data strategy Our mobile data strategy remains the key driver of our success: Mobile data revenue grew by 28.3%. Record smartphone sales add to this momentum: 95% of the hardware we sold were smartphones! ...</description>
      <pubDate>2012-11-06 08:10:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>300</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We are listed! </title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/53453/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <pubDate>2012-10-30 09:30:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>298</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press conference on planned IPO</title>
      <link>http://intranet.de.telefonica/ext/standard/online/53378/tree_42218/index</link>
      <author>Rene Schuster, rene.schuster@telefonica.com</author>
      <pubDate>2012-10-17 18:50:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://intranet.de.telefonica/static/layout/common/image/logo/ceo_blog_rene_310x150.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
      <guid>293</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
